Look, I was gonna go easy on
you and not to hurt your
feelings
But I'm only going to get this
one chance
Something's wrong, I can feel
it (Six minutes, Slim Shady,
you're on)
Just a feeling I've got, like
something's about to happen,
but I don't know what
If that means, what I think it
means, we're in trouble, big
trouble,
And if he is as bananas as you
say, I'm not taking any
chances
You were just what the doctor ordered
I'm beginning to feel like a
Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod
Now who thinks their arms are
long enough to slap box, slap
box?
They said I rap like a robot,
so call me Rapbot
But for me to rap like a
computer must be in my genes
I got a laptop in my back pocket
My pen'll go off when I half-cock it
Got a fat knot from that rap profit
Made a living and a killing off it
Ever since Bill Clinton was
still in office
With Monica Lewinsky feeling
on his nut-sack
I'm an MC still as honest
But as rude and indecent as
all hell syllables, killaholic
(Kill 'em all with)
This slickety, gibbedy, hibbedy hip hop
You don't really wanna get
into a pissing match with this
rappidy rap
Packing a Mac in the back of
the Ac, pack backpack rap,
yep, yackidy-yac
The exact same time I attempt
these lyrical acrobat stunts
while I'm practicing
That I'll still be able to
break a motherfuckin' table
Over the back of a couple of
faggots and crack it in half
Only realized it was ironic I
was signed to Aftermath after
the fact
How could I not blow? All I do
is drop F-bombs, feel my wrath
of attack
Rappers are having a rough
time period, here's a Maxipad
It's actually disastrously bad
For the wack while I'm
masterfully constructing this
masterpiece as
I'm beginning to feel like a
Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod
Now who thinks their arms are
long enough to slap box, slap
box?
Let me show you maintaining
this shit ain't that hard,
that hard
Everybody want the key and the
secret to rap immortality like
I have got
Well, to be truthful the
blueprint's simply rage and
youthful exuberance
Everybody loves to root for a nuisance
Hit the earth like an
asteroid, did nothing but
shoot for the moon since
MC's get taken to school with this music
Cause I use it as a vehicle to
bust a rhyme
Now I lead a new school full of students
Me? I'm a product of Rakim,
Lakim Shabazz, 2Pac N-
-W.A, Cube, hey, Doc, Ren,
Yella, Eazy, thank you, they
got Slim
Inspired enough to one day
grow up, blow up and be in a
position
To meet Run DMC and induct
them into the motherfuckin'
Rock n'
Roll Hall of Fame
Even though I walk in the
church and burst in a ball of
flames
Only Hall of Fame I be
inducted in is the alcohol of
fame
On the wall of shame
You fags think it's all a game
'til I walk a flock of flames
Off of planking, tell me what
in the fuck are you thinking?
Little gay looking boy
So gay I can barely say it
with a straight face looking
boy
You witnessing a massacre
Like you watching a church
gathering take place looking
boy
Oy vey, that boy's gay, that's
all they say looking boy
You get a thumbs up, pat on the back
And a way to go from your
label everyday looking boy
Hey, looking boy, what you say
looking boy?
I got a "hell yeah" from Dre looking boy
I'mma work for everything I have
Never ask nobody for shit, get
outta my face looking boy
Basically boy you're never
gonna be capable
To keep up with the same pace
looking boy
'Cause I'm beginning to feel
like a Rap God, Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod, back nod
The way I'm racing around the
track, call me Nascar, Nascar
Dale Earnhardt of the trailer
park, the White Trash God
Kneel before General Zod this
planet's Krypton, no Asgard,
Asgard
So you be Thor and I'll be
Odin, you rodent, I'm
omnipotent
Let off then I'm reloading
immediately with these bombs
I'm totin'
And I should not be woken
I'm the walking dead, but I'm
just a talking head, a zombie
floating
But I got your mom deep throating
I'm out my ramen noodle, we
have nothing in common, poodle
I'm a doberman, pinch yourself
in the arm and pay homage,
pupil
It's me, my honesty's brutal
But it's honestly futile if I
don't utilize what I do though
For good at least once in a while
So I wanna make sure somewhere
in this chicken scratch I
scribble and doodle
Enough rhymes to maybe to try
and help get some people
through tough times
But I gotta keep a few
punchlines just in case cause
even you unsigned
Rappers are hungry looking at
me like it's lunchtime
I know there was a time where once I
Was king of the underground,
but I still rap like I'm on my
Pharoahe Monch grind
So I crunch rhymes, but
sometimes when you combine
Appeal with the skin color of mine
You get too big and here they
come trying to,
Censor you like that one line
I said on "I'm Back" from the
Marshall Mathers LP
One where I tried to say I
take seven kids from Columbine
Put 'em all in a line, add an
AK-47, a revolver and a nine
See if I get away with it now
that I ain't as big as I was,
but I've
Morphed into an immortal
coming through the portal
You're stuck in a time warp
from 2004 though
And I don't know what the fuck
that you rhyme for
You're pointless as Rapunzel
with fucking cornrows
You're like normal, fuck being normal
And I just bought a new Raygun
from the future
To just come and shoot ya like
when Fabolous made Ray J mad
'Cause Fab said he looked like
a fag at Maywhether's pad
Singin' to a man while they played piano
Man, oh man, that was a 24/7
special on the cable channel
So Ray J went straight to the
radio station the very next
day
"Hey, Fab, I'mma kill you"
Lyrics coming at you at
supersonic speed, (JJ Fad)
Uh, sama lamaa duma lamaa you
assuming I'm a human
What I gotta do to get it
through to you I'm superhuman
Innovative and I'm made of rubber
So that anything you saying
ricocheting off of me and
it'll glue to you
I'm never stating, more than
never demonstrating
How to give a motherfuckin'
audience a feeling like it's
levitating
Never fading, and I know that
the haters are forever waiting
For the day that they can say
I fell off, they'd be
celebrating
Cause I know the way to get
'em motivated
I make elevating music, you
make elevator music
Oh, he's too mainstream
Well, that's what they do when
they get jealous, they confuse
it
It's not hip hop, it's pop,
cause I found a hella way to
fuse it
With rock, shock rap with Doc
Throw on Lose Yourself and
make 'em lose it
I don't know how to make songs like that
I don't know what words to use
Let me know when it occurs to you
While I'm ripping any one of
these verses diverse as you
It's curtains, I'm
inadvertently hurtin' you
How many verses I gotta murder to,
Prove that if you're half as
nice at songs you can
sacrifice virgins too uh!
School flunkie, pill junky
But look at the accolades the
skills brung me
Full of myself, but still hungry
I bully myself cause I make me
do what I put my mind to
And I'm a million leagues
above you, ill when I speak in
tongues
But it's still tongue in cheek, fuck you
I'm drunk so Satan take the
fucking wheel, I'm asleep in
the front seat
Bumping Heavy D and the Boys,
still chunky, but funky
But in my head there's
something I can feel tugging
and struggling
Angels fight with devils,
here's what they want from me
They asking me to eliminate
some of the women hate
But if you take into
consideration the bitter
hatred that I had
Then you may be a little
patient and more sympathetic
to the situation
And understand the discrimination
But fuck it, life's handing
you lemons, make lemonade then
But if I can't batter the
women how the fuck am I
supposed to bake them a cake
then?
Don't mistake it for Satan
It's a fatal mistake if you
think I need to be overseas
And take a vacation to trip a broad
And make her fall on her face
and don't be a retard
Be a king? Think not, why be a
king when you can be a God?
www.RentAnAdviser.com